CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY WARNER BROS .
WE DIDN 'T LIE TO YOU , FOLKS .
WE TOLD YOU WE HAD LIVING , BREATHING MONSTROSITIES .
YOU LAUGHED AT THEM , SHUDDERED AT THEM ,
AND YET , BUT FOR THE ACCIDENT OF BIRTH ,
YOU MIGHT BE EVEN AS THEY ARE .
THEY DID NOT ASK TO BE BROUGHT INTO THE WORLD ,
BUT INTO THE WORLD THEY CAME .
THEIR CODE IS A LAW UNTO THEMSELVES .
OFFEND ONE ,
AND YOU OFFEND THEM ALL .
AND NOW , FOLKS ,
IF YOU 'LL JUST STEP THIS WAY ,
YOU ARE ABOUT TO WITNESS THE MOST AMAZING ,
THE MOST ASTOUNDING LIVING MONSTROSITY
OF ALL TIME .
AAH !
OH !
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
FRIENDS ...
SHE WAS ONCE A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN .
A ROYAL PRINCE SHOT HIMSELF FOR LOVE OF HER .
SHE WAS KNOWN AS THE PEACOCK OF THE AIR .
[ BAND PLAYING WALTZ ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ SPEAKING GERMAN ]
SHE 'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL BIG WOMAN
I HAVE EVER SEEN .
WHY , HANS , HOW YOU TALK !
I SHOULD BE JEALOUS PRETTY SOON .
ACH . DON 'T BE SILLY .
DON 'T BE SILLY ?
I 'VE SEEN THESE WOMENS
MAKING EYES AT MY HANS .
OF COURSE , I AIN 'T JEALOUS .
OH , FRIEDA , MY DEAR ,
I HAVE EYES FOR ONLY ONE WOMAN ...
THE WOMAN I ASKED TO BE MY WIFE .
[ DRUM ROLL ]
FRAULEIN FRIEDA .
[ SPEAKING GERMAN ]
HA .
ARE YOU LAUGHING AT ME ?
WHY , NO , MONSIEUR .
THANKS . I 'M GLAD .
WHY SHOULD I LAUGH AT YOU ?
MOST BIG PEOPLE DO .
THEY DON 'T REALIZE I 'M A MAN ,
WITH THE SAME FEELINGS THEY HAVE .
THANK YOU .
YOU ARE SO KIND , MONSIEUR .
NICE . NICE .
DON 'T . DON 'T .
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ BAND PLAYING MARCH ]
YOU MUST COME TO SEE ME SOMETIME ,
AND WE 'LL HAVE A LITTLE WINE TOGETHER .
DANKE , FRAULEIN CLEO , DANKE .
LAST NIGHT , YOU HAD TOO HEAVY A DINNER ,
AND NOW YOUR IMAGINATION IS ...
BUT , MONSIEUR DUVAL ,
AT FIRST , I COULD NOT BELIEVE MY OWN EYES ...
A LOT OF HORRIBLE , TWISTED THINGS ,
YOU KNOW , CRAWLING , WHINING , LAUGHING ...
BE DONE , JEAN .
WHAT WERE YOU DRINKING LAST NIGHT ?
NOTHING , MONSIEUR , I ASSURE YOU .
OH , MONSIEUR , THERE MUST BE A LAW IN FRANCE
TO SMOTHER SUCH THINGS AT BIRTH
OR ... OR ... OR LOCK THEM UP .
ALL RIGHT , JEAN .
IF THERE 'S ANYTHING LIKE YOU SAY ON MY GROUNDS ,
WE 'LL HAVE THEM REMOVED .
[ HARMONICA PLAYING AND PEOPLE HUMMING NOISILY ]
[ SHOUTING ]
COME ON ! LET 'S GO !
ALL OF YOU ! TOUTE DE SUITE !
TOUTE DE SUITE !
GO AWAY , ALL OF YOU !
DON 'T YOU KNOW TRESPASSING
IS THE SAME AS STEALING ?
OH , I 'M SORRY , MONSIEUR .
I AM MADAME TETRALLINI .
THESE ARE CHILDREN IN MY CIRCUS .
CHILDREN ?
THEY 'RE MONSTERS !
OH , YOUR CIRCUS . I UNDERSTAND .
SO YOU SEE , MONSIEUR ,
WHEN I GET A CHANCE ,
I LIKE TO TAKE THEM INTO THE SUNSHINE
AND LET THEM PLAY LIKE CHILDREN .
THAT IS WHAT MOST OF THEM ARE ...
CHILDREN .
PLEASE FORGET THE ROSSEE , MADAME .
YOU ARE WELCOME TO REMAIN .
AU REVOIR .
COME , JEAN .
THANKS A THOUSAND , MONSIEUR !
A THOUSAND THANKS , MONSIEUR !
OH , SHAME !
SHAME ! SHAME !
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU
NOT TO BE FRIGHTENED ?
HAVE I NOT TOLD YOU
GOD LOOKS AFTER ALL HIS CHILDREN ?
[ MADAME TETRALLINI SINGING IN FRENCH ]
GOOD EVENING , MADAME TETRALLINI .
HOW ARE YOU , MADAME TETRALLINI ?
BIG CROWD TONIGHT .
THERE SHE GOES ,
TAKING THEM OUT TO EXERCISE .
NURSE TO A LOT OF MANGY FREAKS .
AHA !
JUST AS THEY ARE REPRESENTED ON THE BANNER ,
YOU WILL SEE THEM ON THE INSIDE !
LIVING , BREATHING MONSTROSITIES !
JOSEPHINE JOSEPH !
HALF WOMAN ! HALF MAN !
HAVE A CIGAR , JOSEPH .
YOU DROPPED YOUR LIPSTICK , JOSEPHINE .
DON 'T GET HER SORE ,
OR HE 'LL BUST YOU IN THE NOSE .
HA ! HA HA !
COME ON . HURRY UP .
THAT 'S A BOY .
[ SPLASH ]
[ MAN ] YOU 'RE ALL WRONG . I D-D-DIDN 'T DO IT .
[ MAN ] WELL , WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO ? BE FUNNY ?
AW , YOU JUST DON 'T UNDERSTAND .
A ROMAN LADY ...
GETTING OFF THE BULL AND SCRATCHING YOURSELF .
WELL , C-CAN 'T A ROMAN LADY I-I-ITCH ?
WHY DON 'T YOU TAKE A BATH ?
I DID , BUT IT 'S THE BULL
THAT NEEDS THE B-B-BATH .
I THINK SH-SHE ... SH-SHE ...
SH-SHE LIKES YOU .
BUT HE D-D-DON 'T .
HA HA HA HA !
OH , HANS . THOSE FLOWERS YOU SENT TO ME ...
THEY WERE BEAUTIFUL !
BUT NOT MUCH BEAUTIFUL AS YOU .
OH ...
THANK YOU .
AND , HANS ...
I DON 'T LIKE TO ASK ,
BUT MAY I HAVE THE LOAN OF ANOTHER 1,000 FRANCS
UNTIL MY MONEY FROM PARIS ARRIVES ?
WITH PLEASURE ,
FRAULEIN .
THANK YOU .
I 'LL BRING IT TO YOUR WAGON TONIGHT .
OH , FORGET IT . FORGET IT .
MAYBE I WAS JUST FOOLING .
FOOLING ? FOOLING , HUH ?
YEAH .
HA ! " COME , LITTLE GIRL , I WANT TO TAKE CARE OF YOU . "
OH ! AND I FELL FOR THAT !
OH , FORGET IT .
FORGET IT .
SO ... YOU 'RE QUITTING .
IS THAT IT ?
HA HA !
MAYBE I 'M ONLY FOOLING .
WELL , YOU ARE NOT QUITTING ME ...
' CAUSE I 'M KICKING YOU OUT !
OH .
OH , NO , YOU DON 'T .
I GAVE YOU THIS .
OH , WHY , YOU CHEAP ...
OH !
AND DON 'T YOU COME AROUND CRYING TONIGHT ,
TRYING TO GET BACK IN !
I 'M THROUGH WASTING MY TIME AND MONEY
ON THINGS LIKE YOU !
YEAH . YOUR TIME ...
BUT MY MONEY .
UNGRATEFUL LITTLE TRAMP .
AH !
THAT IS FINE .
WELL , WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT ?
DIDN 'T YOU EVER SEE A LADY MOVE BEFORE ?
I GUESS YOU 'VE BEEN LISTENING TO
EVERY WORD HE SAID .
THAT 'S IT . THAT 'S IT .
GO AHEAD AND LAUGH .
IT 'S FUNNY , AIN 'T IT ?
YEAH .
WOMEN ARE FUNNY , AIN 'T THEY ?
THEY 'RE ALL TRAMPS , AIN 'T THEY ?
YEAH .
EXCEPT WHEN YOU CAN GET MONEY FROM THEM !
WELL , I 'LL BE ...
SAY , WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE ,
SHOOTING OFF YOUR HEAD ?
SAY , THIS IS PHROSO ... PHROSO YOU 'RE TALKING TO ,
NOT ANY OF THOSE SLUGS
YOU 'VE BEEN CHASING AROUND WITH .
NOW , YOU LISTEN TO ME .
OH , I DIDN 'T MEAN YOU !
I HAD TO TAKE IT OUT ON SOMEBODY .
YEAH , YOU DAMES IS ALL ALIKE .
YOU 'RE SHARPSHOOTING .
YOU 'RE CHEAP .
AND HOW YOU SQUEAL WHEN YOU GET WHAT 'S COMING TO YOU .
OH . EASY , KID . EASY !
CUT IT !
[ SOBBING ]
OH , IT 'S MY OWN FAULT .
[ SNIFFLING ]
WHAT GETS ME SO COCKEYED SORE AT MYSELF
IS THAT I FELL FOR THAT BIG HUNK OF BEEF !
SO YOU FINALLY GOT WISE TO YOURSELF , DID YOU ?
IT 'S A FUNNY THING ABOUT YOU WOMEN .
MOST OF YOU DON 'T GET WISE SOON ENOUGH .
YOU WAIT UNTIL YOU 'RE SO OLD , NOBODY WANTS YOU .
NOBODY DOES MOST OF THE TIME .
WELL , YOU OUGHT TO BE TICKLED TO DEATH
YOU 'RE WASHED UP WITH HIM .
YOU 'RE NOT SO HARD TO LOOK AT .
GIVE YOURSELF A TUMBLE . YOU 'LL MAKE THE GRADE .
YOUR BREAKS IS COMING .
COMING ? GONE , YOU MEAN .
AW , NOW YOU 'RE GOING TO SIT THERE
FEELING SORRY FOR YOURSELF .
OH , NO , I AIN 'T .
DON 'T YOU EVER ACCUSE ME OF THAT !
ALL RIGHT . ALL RIGHT !
BUT ONE THING ...
DON 'T GO OUT FILLING YOUR HIDE
WITH A LOT OF BOOZE CELEBRATING ,
' CAUSE FUN WHAT 'S GOT THAT WAY NEVER DONE NO ONE NO GOOD .
GET ME ?
I GOT YOU .
SAY ...
YOU 'RE A PRETTY GOOD KID .
YOU 'RE DARN RIGHT I AM .
YOU SHOULD HAVE CAUGHT ME BEFORE MY OPERATION .
HELLO , PHROSO .
TOMORROW NIGHT 'S THE BIG NIGHT , EH , DAISY ?
YES , THE SISTER 'S GETTING MARRIED .
AND I 'M THRILLED TO DEATH .
SHE THRILLS AT ANYTHING .
OH ... ROSCOE 'S A GOOD KID .
SHE 'S ONLY JOKING . SHE 'LL LIKE HIM LOTS
AFTER SHE KNOWS HIM BETTER .
OH , THAT REMINDS ME !
CLOSE YOUR EYES , VIOLET .
GO AHEAD . CLOSE THEM .
WHAT DID I DO ?
PINCHED DAISY 'S ARM .
WELL , WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT !
OH , D-D-D-D ...
DAISY !
HER MASTER 'S VOICE IS CALLING .
GETTING FRESH , EH ?
WELL , I DON 'T LIKE IT ONE B-B-B-B ...
WELL , COME ON . COME ON .
YOU 'LL HAVE TO HURRY . WE HAVEN 'T MUCH TIME .
SO YOU WERE FLIRTING
WITH THAT CH-CHEAP CLOWN , WERE YOU ?
NO , I WASN 'T .
HE WAS DOING A TRICK WITH ME .
YOU SHUT UP .
I 'M M-M-MARRYING YOUR S-S-SISTER ,
NOT YOU-OU .
I SAW HIM GETTING F-F-FAMILIAR WITH YOU .
OH , COME ON , DAISY .
OH , NO , YOU D-D-DON 'T .
SHE 'S GOING TO STAY RIGHT HERE .
NO , SHE ISN 'T . I GOT TO GO .
AW , P-PHOOEY .
YOU 'RE ALWAYS USING THAT FOR AN EXCU ... FOR AN EXCU ...
FOR AN ALIB-B-BI .
♪ OH , TIE THE KNOT FOREVER ♪
[ APPLAUDING ]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
WELL ...
YOU DON 'T LOOK AT OTHERS SO MUCH , DO YOU ?
OH , YES .
I HAVE SEEN YOU .
SO THAT 'S HOW IT IS .
YOU GOT TO BE CAUGHT .
WELL ?
OH ! COME ON IN .
HELP YOURSELF TO A DRINK .
AH ! THAT IS FINE .
FEEL LIKE EATING SOMETHING ?
ALWAYS !
PROSIT .
HOW MANY ?
OH , I 'M NOT VERY HUNGRY .
ABOUT SIX .
HOW DO YOU LIKE THEM ?
NOT BAD .
HO HO !
OH , BUT YOU ARE STRONG .
YOU ARE SQUEEZING ME TO DEATH .
AND YOU 'LL LIKE IT .
OH , YOU ARE TAKING MY BREATH AWAY .
YOU !
NOW HERE 'S SOMETHING FOR YOUR EYE .
HA HA HA HA !
BUT , HANS , MY
LIEBCHEN ,
YOU HAVE NOT BEEN LISTENING
TO A WORD I HAVE BEEN SAYING .
HANS .
YES , FRIEDA ?
YOU HAVE NOT BEEN LISTENING TO ME .
YES , I HAVE , FRIEDA . I HAVE .
THEN WHAT WAS I SAYING ?
YOU WERE SAYING ...
YOU WERE SAYING ... WHAT WERE YOU SAYING ?
I WAS SAYING TONIGHT
YOU MUST NOT SMOKE SUCH A BIG CIGAR .
YOUR VOICE WAS VERY BAD AT TONIGHT 'S SHOW .
PLEASE , FRIEDA , DON 'T TELL ME WHAT I DO .
WHEN I WANT A CIGAR , I SMOKE A CIGAR .
I WANT NO ORDERS FROM A WOMAN .
OH , HANS , THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
SINCE WE HAVE BEEN ENGAGED
YOU HAVE SPOKEN TO ME SO .
WHY IS IT ?
OH , FRIEDCHEN , I 'M SORRY .
I ...
AH ! HERE 'S OUR COFFEE .
HERE IT IS .
FIVE LUMPS FROM SUGAR IN EACH .
WHAT ? FIVE LUMPS ?
OH !
SAY , THE LITTLE APE SENT TO PARIS FOR THIS .
YES , YES . PARIS .
WE 'RE DOING VERY WELL .
BUT I DON 'T LIKE FRUIT .
YOU SHOULD EAT A LOT . IT 'S GOOD FOR YOU .
NEXT TIME , I TELL HIM I LIKE CHAMPAGNE .
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
WHO IS IT ?
IT 'S HANS !
WHO ?
IT 'S HANS .
OH , MY DARLING ,
YOUR BASKET OF FRUIT WAS LOVELY .
BUT I AM , UH ...
I AM TAKING A BATH NOW .
CAN 'T YOU COME BACK LATER ?
YES ,
FRAULEIN .
OH , THANK YOU , DEAR .
[ LAUGHING ]
SHH !
YOU 'LL SPOIL EVERYTHING
IF HE HEARS YOU .
HA !
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ? YOU AIN 'T SINGING , AS USUAL .
OH , THIS MORNING ,
I HAVE SUCH A BIG WASHING TO DO .
HOW 'S HANS ?
I SAID , HOW 'S HANS ?
OH , HANS IS FINE . DANKE . HE 'S FINE .
FRIEDA , SOMETHING 'S WRONG .
WHAT IS IT ?
OH , NOTHING . ONLY ...
WELL , THAT CLEOPATRA WOMAN ...
MY HANS ...
OH , I CANNOT TELL IT .
SHE 'S STILL AFTER HANS , AIN 'T SHE ?
YEAH . ALWAYS SHE 'S SMILING BY HIM .
YEAH . WELL , IF SHE SMILES BY SOMEBODY I KNOW ,
SHE 'LL HAVE TO BUY HERSELF A NEW SET OF TEETH .
ACH . WHY IS IT ,
WE WOMEN ALWAYS HAS GOT TO WORRY ?
OH , IT 'S ALWAYS BEEN THAT WAY .
I GUESS IT ALWAYS WILL BE .
YEAH , AND BY ME , SHE HAS NO SHAME .
ALWAYS WHEN I CAN HEAR IT ,
SHE SAYS TO HIM ,
" MANY THANKS , MY DARLING ,
" FOR THE FLOWERS .
" THANKS , MY DARLING , FOR THIS ,
" AND THANKS , MY DARLING ,
FOR THAT . "
ALWAYS SOMETHING HE HAS GIVEN HER .
AW , DON 'T YOU WORRY , FRIEDA .
HE DOESN 'T LOVE HER .
OH ! THAT BIG HORSE .
YEAH , BUT SHE KEEPS AFTER HIM .
THAT 'S WHY I WORRY .
WHY NOT PINK TIGHTS ?
YOU KNOW . WITH SPANGLES ALL AROUND .
IT WILL SHOW HER FIGURE OFF MORE .
OH , NEIN . NO TIGHTS . WITHOUT TIGHTS .
YOU KNOW , THAT SOFT , FLIMSY
WHAT-YOU-CALL-IT STUFF .
LET HER FIGURE SHOW THROUGH .
WHY NOT LIKE LADY GODIVA ?
HA HA ! HA HA !
JA , THAT 'S IT .
THAT 'S IT , AND I 'LL HIRE HER
TO RIDE THE BACK OF MY BULL .
DUMMKOPF ! WHAT HAVE YOU ON YOUR SHOULDER FOR HEADS ?
SWISS CHEESE ?
HA HA HA !
OH ! OUCH !
WHAT 'S THE MATTER , CLEO ?
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
OH , I THINK I STRAINED MY SHOULDER LAST NIGHT .
GIVE A RUB , WILL YOU ?
[ CLEOPATRA ] FARTHER .
FARTHER .
DOWN .
OVER .
OH , IT 'S SO GOOD TO BE RUBBED !
[ TOGETHER ] OUR CARDS , LADY .
WHAT FOR ?
[ TOGETHER ] A COUPLE OF RUBBERS FROM BERLIN .
[ SPEAKING GERMAN ]
[ BOISTEROUS LAUGHTER ]
THAT REMINDS ME .
I HAD A SWELL DREAM ABOUT YOU LAST NIGHT .
OH , YOU DID ?
YEAH . YOU WERE STANDING
IN A BATHING SUIT ON A ROCK ,
YOU KNOW , LIKE A STATUE .
THE WIND WAS BLOWING THROUGH YOUR HAIR ,
AND THE WAVES WERE WASHING AROUND YOU .
AND YOUR FIGURE ...
HOW IT STOOD OUT .
IT LOOKED GREAT !
SAY !
YOU HAVE GOT A GOOD FIGURE .
OH .
OH , DO YOU THINK SO ?
SURE !
HEY , PHROSO !
DID YOU TRY THAT GAG I TOLD YOU ABOUT ?
YEAH , AND IT WAS A WOW .
GET UP HERE , JOHNNY . I 'LL SHOW IT TO YOU .
I DID EVERYTHING YOU TOLD ME ,
AND IT LAID THEM RIGHT IN THE SAW DUST .
WATCH THIS , VENUS . WATCH THIS .
HELLO , VENUS .
HELLO , JOHNNY .
SAY , PHROSO , WHAT ELSE DID YOU DREAM ?
THEN THE DREAM CHANGED . WE WAS IN PARIS .
PARIS !
YEAH . AT THE OPERA , RIGHT IN THE FRONT BOX .
WE WERE ALL DRESSED UP .
OH , GEE . WHAT DID I HAVE ON ?
AND DID I LOOK SWELL ! EVERYBODY WAS POINTING AT ME .
THEY WERE SAYING , " THAT 'S PHROSO THE CLOWN ! "
AND WAS I EMBARRASSED ! OH !
DID THEY ... DID THEY SAY ANYTHING ABOUT ME ?
SURE , SURE .
WELL , WHAT DID THEY SAY , HUH ?
HIT ME . GO AHEAD . HIT ME !
ON THE HEAD . HIT ME !
[ CLUCKING LIKE A CHICKEN ]
AW , THAT 'S HOW IT IS .
YOU DON 'T THINK IT 'S FUNNY .
IT 'S SAD , IS IT ?
WELL , IT WILL JUST PANIC ' EM .
PHROSO ! PHROSO !
[ WHISPERING ]
NO .
WHEN ?
COME ON !
COME ON ! COME ON , VENUS !
THE BEARDED LADY 'S BABY 'S BORN !
AW !
OH , GEE .
AIN 'T IT CUTE ?
WHAT IS IT ?
A GIRL .
OH , BOY , THAT 'S GREAT ,
AND IT 'S GOING TO HAVE A BEARD .
AH ! HOW 'S THE PROUD FATHER !
WHAT WAS IT ?
A GIRL .
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME .
YOU MIGHT GET A COUPLE OF SMITH BROTHERS .
I TRIED .
PLEASE , VIOLET , PLEASE .
DON 'T QUARREL WITH HIM ANYMORE .
IF HE 'S GOING TO SAY ANYTHING , LET HIM SAY IT .
DON 'T LET HIM P-P-PUFF FOR AN HOUR .
SAY , YOU 'RE GOING TO D-D-DO AS I SAY .
I 'M THE B-B-BOSS OF MY HOME .
HALF OF IT , YOU MEAN .
PLEASE , PLEASE , VIOLET .
HEY , LISTEN HERE .
I D-DON 'T WANT THOSE TR-TRAMPS YOU GO WITH
HANGING AROUND MY WIFE .
OH , BE QUIET !
HOOK UP OUR DRESS .
AW , IF IT ISN 'T YOUR DR-DRESS I 'M H-HOOKING UP ,
IT 'S SOMETHING ELSE .
AND ANOTHER THING ... YOU GOT TO CUT OUT
GETTING DR-DRUNK EVERY NIGHT , TOO .
IS THAT SO ?
YEAH . I 'M NOT GOING TO HAVE MY W-W-WIFE
LAYING IN B-BED HALF THE D-DAY WITH YOUR HANGOVER .
COME ON , DAISY . LET 'S GET OUT OF HERE .
OH , NO , SHE D-DON 'T .
SHE 'S GOING TO ST-STAY RIGHT HERE .
COME ON . I GOT TO GO .
AW , P-P-PHOOEY .
YOU 'RE ALWAYS USING THAT FOR AN EXCU ... FOR AN EXCU ...
FOR AN ALIB-B-BI .
[ HUMMING ]
CLEOPATRA AIN 'T ONE OF US .
WHY , WE 'RE JUST FILTHY THINGS TO HER .
SHE 'D SPIT ON HANS
IF HE WASN 'T GIVING HER PRESENTS .
LET HER TRY IT .
LET HER TRY DOING ANYTHING TO ONE OF US .
YOU 'RE RIGHT .
SHE DON 'T KNOW US ,
BUT SHE 'LL FIND OUT .
THERE YOU ARE .
I KIND OF PEEKED OUT OF THE CORNER OF MY EYE
AND GOT MADAME TETRALLINI GIVING US THE ONCE-OVER .
I GUESS SHE KNOWS SHE 'S GOT A GOOD ACT .
IT ISN 'T ONLY OUR ACT THAT GETS THEM .
WE 'VE GOT PERSONALITY .
WE KNOW HOW TO SELL THE STUFF ...
SAME WAY IN THE LAST TOWN .
NEVER HEARD SUCH APPLAUSE IN YOUR LIFE .
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING
THAT EVERYBODY AROUND HERE DON 'T KNOW .
WE 'RE ONLY KILLING TIME WITH THIS CIRCUS .
WE 'VE GOT BIGGER TIME TO FOLLOW ,
AND WE CAN DO IT , TOO .
WELL , CATCH OUR ACT TOMORROW NIGHT .
WE GOT SOMETHING NEW .
I CAN DO ANYTHING WITH MY MOUTH !
OH , SCHLITZE , WHAT A PRETTY DRESS !
OH , HOW BEAUTIFUL YOU LOOK TONIGHT !
YOU 'RE JUST A MAN 'S WOMAN .
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN , HUH ? YOU .
IF YOU 'RE A GOOD GIRL WHEN I GET TO PARIS ,
I 'LL BUY YOU A BIG HAT
WITH A LONG , BEAUTIFUL FEATHER ON IT .
OH , HELLO , ELVIRA .
HI .
HELLO , JENNIE LEE .
LOOK .
HASN 'T SCHLITZE GOT A BEAUTIFUL DRESS ?
ISN 'T THAT PRETTY ? WHEN I GET TO PARIS ,
I 'M GOING TO BUY HER A BIG HAT
WITH A LONG FEATHER ON IT ,
AND IF YOU 'RE GOOD GIRLS ,
WHEN I GET TO PARIS , I 'LL BUY YOU A HAT
WITH A BIGGER FEATHER ON IT .
SO WHAT ?
[ SPEAKING UNINTELLIGIBLY ]
WHY , SCHLITZE , WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
OH ! I 'M SORRY , SCHLITZE !
[ SCHLITZE SPEAKING UNINTELLIGIBLY ]
HE WAS OUT THERE AGAIN TONIGHT .
HE FOLLOWED YOU FROM THE LAST TOWN .
IF EDDIE SEES IT , THERE 'LL BE A FIGHT .
WELL , IT AIN 'T YOUR FAULT .
AH , THERE YOU ARE , FRANCES . THOUGHT YOU 'D GONE TO BED .
HELLO , ROLLO .
HEAR THAT CROWD OUT THERE AGAIN TONIGHT ?
I BET YOU THOUGHT THE TENT WAS ON FIRE , HUH ?
WELL , IT WASN 'T .
JUST THE ROLLO BROTHERS PANICKING THEM AGAIN .
BUT THEN WE DO IT IN EVERY TOWN .
WE 'RE SO USED TO IT , IT 'S GETTING MONOTONOUS .
SAY , YOU WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT OUR ACT TOMORROW NIGHT .
CAREFUL , CAREFUL . DON 'T WASTE ANY OF IT .
LOOK HOW IT SPARKLES .
LIKE YOUR EYES .
DANCING , GAY , LIKE BUBBLES .
OH , IT 'S DELICIOUS .
MMM ! NICE . NICE .
IT COMES BY THE FINEST VINEYARDS OF FRANCE .
AND YOU SENT FOR IT SPECIALLY FOR ME ?
FOR THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
IN ALL THE WORLD .
DARLING .
HELLO THERE , BABY . WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN SO LONG ?
YOU 'RE A FUNNY GUY , PHROSO .
SOMETIMES YOU PANIC ME .
DON 'T I KNOW IT ?
I PANIC THE WORLD BECAUSE I USE MY NOODLE .
I THINK UP FUNNY GAGS . I MAKE THE WORLD LAUGH .
WITH ME , CLOWNING IS AN ART .
HEY , WHY THE HAT ?
THE HEAD COLD ?
THOUGHT YOU AND ME
HAD A DATE TO GO OUT .
OH , I FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT .
WELL , I 'M INTO THIS NOW .
I 'VE GOT TO GO THROUGH WITH IT .
WELL , MAKE IT SNAPPY , WILL YA ?
I 'M ALL DOLLED UP FOR THE OCCASION .
SORRY , KID . CAN 'T DO IT NOW .
WE 'LL MAKE IT SOME OTHER TIME , HUH ?
AW , DON 'T FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT IT .
I JUST GOT THIS IDEA ALL OF A SUDDEN .
I 'VE GOT TO FINISH IT .
HEY , FUNNY GAG , ISN 'T IT ?
YEAH . I 'M LAUGHING MYSELF SICK .
OH , SAY , COME ON !
HONEY , HEY . COME ON .
COME ON . COME ON .
NOW , NOW , NOW , NOW .
THAT 'S MUCH BETTER .
OH ...
GEE , THAT 'S THE FIRST TIME YOU EVER DONE THAT .
IT AIN 'T THE FIRST TIME I FELT LIKE DOING IT .
YEAH ?
OH , VENUS !
GEE , PHROSO .
I DON 'T MIND TELLING YOU
I 'VE WANTED TO DO THIS FOR A LONG TIME .
OH , PHROSO .
WELL , WE 'RE ALL SET NOW , HEY , VENUS ?
YEAH .
ALL SET NOW .
PLEASE . PLEASE DO .
DON 'T YOU WANT TO MAKE ME HAPPY ?
YES , BUT I DON 'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY .
JUST SAY YES , DEAR .
WILL YOU ?
YES .
OH , VIOLET !
YOU GOT A GOOD WIFE . YOU 'RE HAPPY .
OH , IT 'S THAT SISTER-IN-LAW OF MINE .
SHE WANTS TO SIT UP HALF THE NIGHT
AND R-R-READ .
GEE , THAT 'S TOUGH .
TOUGH ? YOU B-B-B ...
GOOD NIGHT , DARLING .
GOOD NIGHT ,
FRAULEIN .
CLEO 'S GONE ON A D-D-D-D-DIET .
HA HA HA HA !
AWFULLY SWEET OF YOU TO SAY THAT .
AND I KNOW VIOLET WILL BE HAPPY .
OH , HERE 'S ROSCOE .
HELLO .
ROSCOE , THIS IS MR. ROGERS .
GLAD TO M-M-M-MEET YOU .
VIOLET AND HE ARE ENGAGED TO BE MARRIED .
OH , YEAH ?
YES , AND YOU MUST COME TO SEE US SOMETIME .
THANKS . AND YOU MUST COME
TO VI-VI-VI ...
UH , COME TO SEE US SOMETIME , TOO .
I CERTAINLY WILL . THANKS .
WHO IS IT ?
IT 'S FRIEDA , HANS .
MAY I COME IN ?
YES , FRIEDA .
NOW THAT I 'M HERE ,
I DON 'T KNOW HOW TO SAY IT ,
HOW TO MAKE YOU UNDERSTAND .
IF YOU KNEW HOW I FEEL , HANS ,
TO COME TO YOU ABOUT HER .
OH , FRIEDA . I 'M SO SORRY .
I DON 'T WANT TO HURT YOU ,
BUT ICH KANNE NICHT HELFEN .
IF YOU COULD BE HAPPY , HANS ,
I WOULD NOT CARE .
BUT I AM HAPPY , FRIEDA .
NEVER IN MY LIFE WAS I SO HAPPY .
NO , HANS . YOU THINK IT ONLY .
FOR YOU , SHE CANNOT BRING HAPPINESS .
AH , FRIEDA ! YOU DON 'T KNOW .
BUT I DO , HANS .
YOU THINK BECAUSE SHE 'S SO BEAUTIFUL
AND I 'M JUST A ...
DON 'T , HANS . PLEASE .
TO ME , YOU 'RE A MAN ,
BUT TO HER , YOU 'RE ONLY SOMETHING TO LAUGH AT .
THE WHOLE CIRCUS , THEY MAKE FUN
ABOUT YOU AND HER .
LET THEM LAUGH . THE SWINE !
I LOVE HER ! THEY CAN 'T HURT ME .
BUT THEY HURT ME .
FRIEDA , I HAVE BEEN A COWARD .
I SHOULD HAVE COME TO YOU IN THE BEGINNING .
PLEASE FORGIVE ME .
YES , HANS , I FORGIVE YOU .
IT IS ONLY THAT YOU
SHOULD BE HAPPY I WANT .
FRIEDA .
YOU WON 'T WORRY NOW , WILL YOU ?
NO , I WON 'T WORRY .
NICE ! VERY NICE , HMM ?
IT 'S PLATINUM !
SAY , WHERE DO YOU THINK
THE LITTLE POLLIWOG IS GETTING HIS MONEY ?
HA HA HA !
LISTEN AT HIM ! GETTING SO PARTICULAR .
WHAT DO YOU CARE WHERE THE MONEY COMES FROM ?
HOW MUCH IT 'S WORTH ?
WE GOT 500 FOR THE BRACELET ,
BUT THIS LOOKS LIKE THOUSANDS !
I THINK NEXT TIME I 'LL TAKE A FUR COAT .
SAY , THAT LITTLE APE 'S GOT IDEAS ABOUT YOU .
JEALOUS ?
ME ? I 'D SQUISH HIM LIKE A BUG !
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
THAT 'S HIS KNOCK . I 'LL GET RID OF HIM .
GO QUICKLY .
COME IN .
WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
IT 'S ABOUT HANS .
WELL ? I 'M LISTENING .
IT 'S BEHIND HIS BACK .
EVERYBODY 'S LAUGHING
BECAUSE HE 'S IN LOVE WITH YOU .
GO ON .
I KNOW YOU JUST MAKE FUN ,
BUT HANS , HE DOES NOT KNOW THIS .
IF HE FINDS OUT ,
NEVER AGAIN WILL BE HAPPY .
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
THAT I AM JUST MAKING FUN ?
YOU 'RE BIG , SO BEAUTIFUL ...
AND HANS IS SO LITTLE , SO CUTE , HUH ?
WELL , MAYBE I 'M GOING TO MARRY HIM .
IF YOU MARRY , IT WILL BE AT YOU
THEY LAUGH AND STARE .
THAT 'S GOOD ! NOTHING LIKE BEING DIFFERENT .
CLEOPATRA , QUEEN OF THE EARTH ,
MARRIED TO A DWARP ...
HA HA !
A DWARF .
A DWARP !
THEN IT 'S NOT FOR HANS YOU CARE .
IT 'S THE MONEY .
MONEY ?
YOU LITTLE MIND READER .
AH , HE HAS TOLD YOU
OF THE FORTUNE HE HAS INHERITED .
ALWAYS HE SWEAR TO ME TO TELL NO ONE
UNTIL AFTER WE LEAVE THE CIRCUS .
A FORTUNE ?
AND FANCY YOU KNOWING ABOUT IT , TOO .
WELL , I CAN 'T BE ANGRY AT HIM FOR THAT .
NO .
YOU CANNOT DO THIS .
NO ?
HMM .
YOU WAIT AND SEE .
PLEASE .
YOU CAN 'T !
A FORTUNE ! I BET THE LITTLE APE 'S WORTH BILLIONS !
HA HA HA !
A FORTUNE ! CAN YOU BEAT THAT ?
A FORTUNE ! AND I HAVE HIM LIKE THAT .
A SHREWD LITTLE HANS .
HE KNEW ENOUGH TO KEEP HIS MOUTH SHUT .
I COULD MARRY HIM .
YES , HE WOULD MARRY ME !
HA HA HA HA !
MIDGETS ARE NOT STRONG .
HE COULD GET SICK .
HOW ?
IT COULD BE DONE . DONE . I KNOW IT .
[ MUSIC AND LAUGHTER ]
AW , COME ON , MY LITTLE PRECIOUS !
COME ON . LET 'S DRINK .
BIG , HAPPY DRINK . COME ON !
HA HA !
QUIET ! BE QUIET !
HEY , K-KOO KOO !
GIVE SOMEBODY ELSE A CHANCE !
ALL RIGHT , P-PROFESSOR !
A WALTZ , PLEASE .
SHOW HIM UP , VOLCANO ! BURN HIM UP !
OUR WEDDING NIGHT !
HA HA HA HA !
WHAT A THRILL !
NEVER BEFORE DID I THINK
I SHOULD BE SO LUCKY .
LUCKY ... HA HA HA ...
I AM THE LUCKY ONE !
MY LITTLE HANS .
MY CLEO 'S HAPPY . HAPPY !
HAPPY ? HA HA HA ...
[ HERCULES LAUGHING ]
OH , I AM SO HAPPY !
I EVEN COULD KISS YOU , YOU BIG , HOMELY BRUTE !
OH , MY LITTLE GREEN-EYED MONSTER .
MY HUSBAND IS JEALOUS ! HA HA !
HE LOVES ME !
HA HA HA HA HA !
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
COME , MY LITTLE LOVER .
DRINK TO THE HAPPINESS OF YOUR LOVING " WIPE . "
ATTENTION ! ATTENTION !
WE 'LL MAKE HER ONE OF US !
A LOVING CUP ! A LOVING CUP !
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE , GOOGOO-GOGGLE ♪
♪ ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE ♪
♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE ... ♪
THEY 'RE GOING TO MAKE YOU ONE OF THEM .
MY , BIG LUCK !
♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE , GOOGOO-GOGGLE ♪ GOOGOO-GOGGLE !
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , WE ACCEPT HER ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT HER , ONE OF US ♪
♪ WE ACCEPT YOU , WE ACCEPT YOU ♪
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ... ♪
[ HERCULES ] THEY 'RE GOING TO MAKE YOU ONE OF THEM , MY DEAR !
♪ ONE OF US , ONE OF US ♪
♪ GOOBA-GOBBLE , GOOBA-GOBBLE ... ♪
YOU ...
DIRTY ...
SLIMY ... ♪ ONE OF ... ♪
FREAKS !
FREAKS ! FREAKS !
GET OUT OF HERE !
YOU ! OUT !
[ HERCULES ] GET OUT ! YOU HEARD HER !
GET OUT ! HA HA HA HA !
HA HA HA HA !
YOU FIENDS !
MAKE ME ONE OF YOU , WILL YOU ?
WELL , WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ?
WHAT ARE YOU , A MAN OR A BABY ?
PLEASE ! PLEASE !
YOU MAKE ME ASHAMED .
ASHAMED ! YOU ?
WELL , HOLY JUMPING CHRISTMAS !
WHAT MUST I DO ?
MUST I PLAY GAMES WITH YOU ?
MUST MAMMA TAKE YOU HORSEYBACK RIDE ?
HA HA ! THAT 'S IT . HORSEYBACK RIDE !
HA HA HA !
COME , COME , MY LITTLE FLY SPECK .
MAMMA IS GOING TO TAKE YOU
HORSEYBACK RIDE .
COME ON !
GIDDY-UP ! GIDDY-UP , HORSEY !
♪ LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ... ♪
AH , FORGET IT , HANS .
SHE IS SORRY . I 'M SORRY .
DIDN 'T I TOLD YOU SHE WAS DRUNK ?
DIDN 'T I TOLD YOU
WE WAS ONLY HAVING A LITTLE FUN ?
PLEASE .
I ... I UNDERSTAND ...
EVERYTHING .
NO , YOU DON 'T . I TELL YOU ,
THERE 'S NOTHING BETWEEN ME AND CLEO .
OH , BE QUIET ! HAVEN 'T YOU DONE
ENOUGH DAMAGE FOR ONE NIGHT ?
DON 'T YOU REALIZE
WHAT I 'M BEING ACCUSED OF ?
I AIN 'T GOING TO BE BLAMED
FOR SOMETHING I HAVE NOT DONE .
I DON 'T BLAME YOU , CLEO .
I DON 'T BLAME HERCULES .
ONLY ME ,
MYSELF .
NOW YOU 'RE TALKING !
TALKING LIKE A MAN . HA HA !
YOU FOOL !
ALWAYS I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU WOULD ONLY LAUGH AT ME .
MY SWEET ! I 'D RATHER FALL FROM THE TRAPS
AND BREAK MY NECK
THAN HURT YOUR FEELINGS .
DO YOU UNDERSTAND NOW ?
IT WAS ONLY JOKE .
OUR WEDDING ... A JOKE .
NOW I KNOW HOW FUNNY IT IS .
HANS THE MIDGET .
HA !
HANS THE FOOL !
TELL IT IN DIVORCE COURT ! THEY 'LL LAUGH !
EVERYWHERE , THEY 'RE LAUGHING ! LAUGHING !
LAUGHING ! LAUGHING !
OH !
YOU GIVE HIM TOO MUCH .
NO , I HAVEN 'T .
I KNOW WHAT I AM DOING .
COME ON . PICK HIM UP .
DOCTOR , WHAT IS IT ? WHAT CAUSED IT ?
POISON .
A VERY BAD CASE OF PTOMAINE POISONING .
DOCTOR , DID I DO WRONG , THEN ,
GIVING HIM MUSTARD WATER ?
NO .
PROBABLY SAVED HIS LIFE .
NEVER BEFORE DID HE DRINK LIKE THAT ,
BUT SHE KEPT MAKING HIM
AND MAKING HIM .
DRINK , HUH ?
YOU BETTER GET CLEO TO TELL THE DOCTOR
WHAT SHE PUT IN THAT WINE LAST NIGHT .
I DON 'T KNOW WHAT YOU 'RE TALKING ABOUT .
THE STUFF SHE PUT IN THE WINE .
YOU 'RE CRAZY .
YOU CAN 'T GET AWAY WITH IT .
I 'LL TELL THE COPPERS .
SO ... TELL ON YOUR OWN PEOPLE ?
MY PEOPLE ARE DECENT CIRCUS FOLKS , NOT DIRTY RATS
WHAT WOULD KILL A FREAK TO GET HIS MONEY .
YOU DIRTY LITTLE ...
AH , YOUR IMAGINATION 'S GETTING THE BEST OF YOU .
YEAH , MAYBE IT IS ,
BUT COPPERS DON 'T HAVE IMAGINATIONS ,
SO I 'VE BEEN TOLD .
DON 'T MAKE ME HAVE TO GO TO THEM .
CLEO .
YES ?
IT HAS BEEN A WEEK TONIGHT
SINCE WE HAVE BEEN MARRIED .
A WEEK SINCE I HAVE SAID
ALL THOSE THINGS TO YOU .
DON 'T ! DON 'T !
NEVER CAN I FORGIVE MYSELF
FOR WHAT I 'VE SAID .
I 'VE FORGOTTEN IT .
NOTHING MATTERS EXCEPT FOR YOU TO BE WELL .
SO GOOD YOU ARE BY ME , CLEO .
I MUST FIX YOUR MEDICINE , OR I 'LL BE LATE .
I 'LL BE SOON BACK , MY LITTLE .
DON 'T BE LONELY .
I 'LL NEVER FORGET
WHAT YOU ARE DOING FOR ME , CLEO .
BUT IT 'S WHAT I WANT TO DO , MY DARLING .
NOW ... NOW I MUST HURRY .
CLEO .
YES .
WILL YOU LEAVE THE DOOR OPEN , PLEASE ?
YES , MY DARLING .
TONIGHT .
THEY WILL BE READY .
ALL RIGHT . YOU COME TO MY WAGON .
" I MUST HURRY NOW AND FIX YOUR MEDICINE , MY DARLING ,
OR I WILL BE LATE . "
" DIRTY ...
" SLIMY ...
FREAKS ! "
[ THUNDER ]
HE 'S WAITING .
FINE . FINE .
SOON WE GO .
AH , YOU 'RE IMAGINING THINGS !
NO ! THEN I HEAR HERCULES TELL CLEO ,
" VENUS KNOWS TOO MUCH . "
HERCULES ? VENUS ?
YES .
OH , HO !
THANKS , FRIEDA .
[ PLAYING MUSIC ]
MY LITTLE , YOU MUST GO TO SLEEP .
YOUR FRIENDS BETTER GO NOW .
I LIKE THEM HERE .
NO , NO , NO , HANS .
THEY CAN COME BACK TOMORROW .
I WILL GIVE YOU YOUR MEDICINE
AND GET YOU OVER THIS .
GO . GO ON , ALL OF YOU . QUICK , QUICK .
WHAT 'S THIS ?
GIVE ME THAT LITTLE BLACK BOTTLE .
BOTTLE .
YOU GOT THIS BOTTLE OF POISON TO KILL .
[ KICKING DOOR ]
PHROSO !
GET OUT , VENUS !
DO I HAVE TO BUST YOU IN THE JAW
TO MAKE YOU GET OUT ?
[ CLEO SCREAMING ]
GET OUT , VENUS ! GET OUT !
HELP ME !
AAH ! AAH !
HERCULES ! HERCULES ! HERCULES !
[ MAN SCREAMING ]
OH !
AAH !
HANS ! PLEASE , HANS !
HOW SHE GOT THAT WAY WILL NEVER BE KNOWN .
SOME SAY A JEALOUS LOVER .
OTHERS , THAT IT WAS THE CODE OF THE FREAKS .
OTHERS , THE STORM .
BELIEVE IT OR NOT , THERE SHE IS .
[ SQUAWKING ]
BUT , SIR , THEY INSIST ON SEEING YOU .
IN ALL THESE YEARS , I 'VE SEEN NO ONE .
HAVE I NOT TOLD YOU THAT ?
SEND THEM AWAY .
VERY GOOD , SIR .
I CAN 'T SEE NO ONE .
EXCUSE ME , SIR . YOU CAN 'T COME IN .
CAN 'T I ? WHO 'S GOING TO STOP ME ?
I HAVE MY ORDERS .
WELL , I 'M IN , AIN 'T I ?
OH , YES , YOU CAN , HANSIE , OLD BOY .
THERE 'S SOMEONE YOU 'VE JUST GOT TO SEE .
WHY DID YOU COME HERE ?
PLEASE , HANS , DON 'T BE ANGRY .
VENUS AND PHROSO HAVE BEEN SO KIND BY ME .
PLEASE , GO AWAY .
I CAN 'T SEE NO ONE .
BUT , HANS , YOU TRIED TO STOP THEM .
IT WAS ONLY THE POISON YOU WANTED .
IT WASN 'T YOUR FAULT .
DON 'T . DON 'T CRY , HANS .
COME TO ME , MY LIEBCHEN .
DON 'T CRY .
DON 'T , HANS .
DON 'T CRY . I LOVE YOU .
I LOVE YOU .
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY WARNER BROS .